虽然没有新三也没有NFC口也没有Amiibo
不过我想试试文件，不知道是正常Dump还是
毕竟是刚拿到某些Key
fs.writeFileSync('AmiiboAPIKey.bin',new Buffer('3991AACE52DFF922B07A916864CD9528','hex'))
fs.writeFileSync('keyslot0x39DevKeyY.bin',new Buffer('E02D27441DB9558BAD087FD746DF1057','hex'))
fs.writeFileSync('keyslot0x39RetKeyY.bin',new Buffer('ED7858A8BBA7EED7FC970C5979BC0AF2','hex'))

那个我就不知道了，我还是今天才知道的密钥和那个工具。			
密匙我有，目前还是要继续解开如何修改amiibo数据的问题			
amiitool加密用的密钥是3991AACE52DFF922B07A916864CD9528			
linux的程序，其实不完全解密，已经要到用户key了，可以解密修改在加密，大部分文件研究搞定，目前改角色还是遇到问题，有兴趣可以一起研究下			
github上现在有工具amiitool可以用于解密Amiibo了。			


http://chaosgamez.com/threads/most-complete-amiibo-set.7467/




Howdy everyone, this is a hub thread for amiibo bin files.

These files are useful for anyone with an Amiiqo, an N2 Elite, NaMiiO, or Datel PowerSaves for Amiibo. They should also work fine with TagMo when flashed to NTAG215's, they can be used with the Cemu Emulator to emulate amiibo functionality in games.

If you plan on using an Amiiqo or N2 Elite, I highly recommend using the new N2 Elite App that was recently released. For anyone curious on Amiibo, @funfair91 and I created a Google Spreadsheet explaining the ID format for amiibo as well as all known IDs for the amiibo that are out there. It's still a little rough around the edges, but it definitely is easy to learn how amiibo are identified and read with it.

What we have here is a curated, clean, organized collection of amiibo available for download.
We won't waste your time with bad dumps, and we won't waste your time with resetting the data on the amiibo.

Any time a new dump comes out, it's checked out, confirmed that it contains no save data, wiped if it does, and then placed in it's spot inside the collection.

Last Updated: July 27th, 2017

[​IMG]
697 unique amiibo bins
105 Powersave bins
1 copy of the Amiibo Retail Encryption Keys
Completeness: 100%

Detailed Stats Rundown
140/140 released amiibo figures collected (100%)
5/5 amiibo plush toys collected (100%)
552/552 released amiibo cards collected (100%)
105 Optional Amiibo "Powersaves"
​
List of Amiibo and what is/isn't included right now.
Animal Crossing Amiibo Figures (16/16)
Animal Crossing Amiibo Cards
Series 1 Cards (100/100)
Series 2 Cards (100/100)
Series 3 Cards (100/100)
Series 4 Cards (100/100)
Amiibo Festival Cards (3/3)
Character Parfait Cards (2/2)
Welcome Amiibo Series (50/50)
Animal Crossing x Sanrio Series (6/6)
Kirby Amiibo Figures (4/4)
Chibi-Robo Amiibo Figure (1/1)
Monster Hunter Stories Amiibo Figures (6/6)
Pokkén Tournament Amiibo Card (1/1)
Shovel Knight Amiibo Figure (1/1)
Skylanders SuperChargers Amiibo Figures (4/4)
Splatoon Amiibo Figures (11/11)
Pikmin Amiibo Figure (1/1)
Super Mario Amiibo Figures (15/15)
Super Mario Bros. 30th Anniversary Amiibo Figures (2/2)
BoxBoy! Amiibo Figure (1/1)
Fire Emblem Amiibo Figures (2/2)
Mario Sports Amiibo Cards (90/90)
Super Smash Bros Amiibo Figures (63/63)
The Legend of Zelda Amiibo Figures
The Legend of Zelda Twilight Princess Wolf Link Amiibo Figure (1/1)
The Legend of Zelda 30th Anniversary Amiibo Figures (7/7)
The Legend of Zelda Breath of The Wild Amiibo Figures (5/9) (4 are not yet released)
Yoshi's Woolly World Amiibo Plush Toys (5/5)
Also Included:
A Readme containing dumper credits. (readme.txt)
The Amiibo Retail Encryption Keys (key_retail.bin)

Legend:
Red [All are currently missing and planned for inclusion when the are released]
Blue [Known Incomplete, currently being sought after. See post #3 below for a list]
Orange [Partial Completion, see sub info for details]
Yellow [Temporarily Complete, more figures are known to be coming out soon]
Green [Totally Complete, no more figures are coming out either, this is 100% done]

Hidden Content:
**Hidden Content: You must click 'Like' before you can see the hidden data contained here.**
We need help getting dumps of Missing Amiibo!
Scroll down for a list of missing and upcoming Amiibo- and dump them with the official N2 Elite App!
Files should come out to be 572 byte- I also accept dumps that are 540 byte but 572 byte are preferred for archival purposes.

Credits (aka everyone I got bins from)
Spoiler

FAQ

Q: How do I use these bin files?
A: As stated above, a variety of devices and programs can make use of amiibo bin files. The most popular use of them are N2/Amiiqo devices, which are small plastic disks that contain a microcontroller and an NFC tag simulator. The other popular way is by making fake amiibo out of NTAG215s using the TagMo android app.

Q: How do I use the new "Powersaves"?
A: The Amiibo "Powersaves" we have are just Amiibo Bin files, much like the standard set, but they include save files or are hacked in some way to offer an advantage of some sort. Meaning that you can use them in any way you want, just like the standard set.

Q: How can I talk to you?
A: There's more than one of us working on this set, but you can find me on #N2Elite on Efnet or on Discord at CheatFreak#3799.

Q: How do I use the key_retail.bin?
A: This is included for users of the TagMo android app mostly- this is a file containing both retail keys for the Nintendo Figurine Platform- allowing you to essentially create your own legitimate amiibo NFC tags out of Blank NTAG215s. To input it into TagMo, simply copy it to your mobile device, and then inside the TagMo app- click the "..." icon on the top left, and choose "Load Key(s) File..." and select the 'key_retail.bin' from your device storage.

Looking for the like button? 
After you've registered and signed in
It's down here [​IMG] (somewhere)​
#1cheatfreak47, Sep 22, 2016  Last edited: Yesterday at 7:34 PM
martin-one, Wiifan420, Sibot Luciph and 9,164 others like this.
 Cha0s Em3rald
Cha0s Em3raldCha0s Em3rald is a Verified  Member
Administrator
Staff Member
Administrator
Joined:Oct 1, 2015
Messages:3,919
Likes Received:172,960
Thanks for the share @cheatfreak47 

Thread stickied
#2Cha0s Em3rald, Sep 22, 2016
Derrythe, wade1212, ACELEE and 191 others like this.
 cheatfreak47
cheatfreak47cheatfreak47 is a Verified  Member
Uploader
Staff Member
Uploader
Joined:Apr 28, 2016
Messages:157
Likes Received:10,765
Outright Missing Amiibos:
None! :)

Unreleased Amiibo:
Metroid - Samus Aran (coming in september)
Metroid - Metroid (coming in september)

Fire Emblem - Chrom (coming in september)
Fire Emblem - Tiki (coming in september)

Super Mario Odyssey - Goomba (coming october)
Super Mario Odyssey - Koopa Troopa (coming october)
Super Mario Odyssey - Mario (Wedding) (coming october)
Super Mario Odyssey - Peach (Wedding) (coming october)
Super Mario Odyssey - Bowser (Wedding) (coming october)

The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild - Mipha (coming november/december?)
The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild - Daruk (coming november/december?)
The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild - Revali (coming november/december?)
The Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild - Urbosa (coming november/december?)
#3cheatfreak47, Oct 5, 2016  Last edited: Yesterday at 7:35 PM